# **Anicia Snell**



### Software Engineer in Fort Lauderdale, FL

I've been working since the age of 16 at a plethora of places, in my experience I have learned so much and gained the essential tools of how to operate a functional and successful business. Each day passing is an opportunity to learn something grand and to take each lesson learned and put it into play with a company that wants to make a difference in the world.

**PHONE** 954-483-0242 | **EMAIL** anicia.snell.as@icloud.com **GITHUB** https://github.com/ShaolinSunset | **LINKEDIN** https://www.linkedin.com/in/anicia-snell-170953180/

# Milk Match — Peer to Peer milk sharing platform

• Designing a social platform to link mothers and fathers to sources of milk for the parents that are unable to produce.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Server — RA Sushi, Pembroke Pines, FL

March 2019- Present

 Delivered friendly and efficient service to ensure a pleasant dining experience for all guests. Maintained knowledge of current menu items, garnishes, ingredients and preparation methods. Used correct cleaning, sanitizing and food handling. Procedures to maintain optimal protection for customers.

# **Lead Pawnbroker** — Value Pawn, Margate, FL

October 2019 - March 2019

 Manage open and closing functions of store daily as well as leading a small team of 4-6 employees. Performing in house audits and markdowns on necessary inventory, processing supply shipments for store needs, applied payments to loan accounts.

#### **CSR and Supervisor** — Chewy, Hollywood, FL

February 2018 - October 2018

- Oversaw team of 12-15 representatives, upon promotion to Supervisor.
   Analyzed team and individual statistics; prepared reports; devised and implemented incentive programs to improve metrics while maintaining quality. Provided performance coaching and strategies for career development for reps.
- Answered inbound phone calls warmly, process refunds/replacements, take orders, answer emails, update customer accounts (billing information). Escalation calls handled with respect.

#### **EDUCATION & VOLUNTEER**

**LaunchCode,** LC101 Programming Course — 2018 **48in48,** Volunteer Non-Profit, Web Developer — 2020

#### **SKILLS**

# PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- · C#
- Python
- · HTML5/CSS3

#### **FRAMEWORKS**

·.NET

#### **DATABASES**

MySQL

